http://www.tullahomanews.com/site/privacy.html

Today's Top Story
Arrowheads Museum refuses to revert the land back to Coffee County
Dec 9, 2020
The Coffee County Manchester Tullahoma Museum, Inc., which operates the Arrowheads Aerospace Museum, denies that the land and the building should revert to Coffee County.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Dec. 9 COVID-19 Update
Arrowheads Museum refuses to revert the land back to Coffee County
Man opens fire while high on cocaine
Fans meet ‘Bo Duke’ at movie premiere
Committee nixes bonuses for county employees
Governor authorizes National Guard to help at hospitals
Tour of Homes goes virtual with help from Dustin Lynch
County up to 45 COVID-19 deaths
News
Local News
8 hrs ago
According to the latest report from the Tennessee Department of Health, Coffee County is listed with 3,460 total cases of COVID-19. There are currently 429 active cases, 2,985 inactive/recovered cases and 46 deaths from the virus, per the report.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Dec. 9 COVID-19 Update
Arrowheads Museum refuses to revert the land back to Coffee County
Man opens fire while high on cocaine
Fans meet ‘Bo Duke’ at movie premiere
Committee nixes bonuses for county employees
Governor authorizes National Guard to help at hospitals
Tour of Homes goes virtual with help from Dustin Lynch
County up to 45 COVID-19 deaths
Sports
Local Sports
8 hrs ago
After dominating Rockvale 60-21 early on Tuesday, the Tullahoma High School boys wrestling team was able to hold on for a 39-33 home win over Siegel to move to 3-0 on the season.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Farrell's outburst leads Lady Wildcats to win
Wildcats scratch out win over Huntland
Wildcats open season with 40-35 victory
Bobcats down Panthers 36-18
Lady Bobcats hold on for 25-21 win over Lady Panthers
19 Tullahoma football players named as all-region selections
THS basketball teams forced to make changes
Wildcats rally for first win of season
Living
Community Calendar
Education
Health
Religion
Local Inserts
Digital Circulars
Coupons
Today's Living
More 'Walls for Women' coming next spring
STAFF WRITER Erin McCullough
Dec 5, 2020
Following the successful “Walls for Women” public art campaign this year, Tullahoma-based public art advocacy organization Do More Art - Events (DMA) will be expanding the female-driven campaign into 2021, thanks to a partnership with the Tennessee Arts Commission.
Read All Living
More Headlines
Trees of Christmas premieres Wednesday at South Jackson
Finding a Forrest in the trees
Having Faith for miracles
So you say it’s your birthday?
Dee Foster Fine Art wows art center guests
Master Gardeners looking for green thumbs
Moorehead named to art center board
Tullahoma celebrates passage of 19th Amendment
Arts & Entertainment
Local Entertainment
Movies
Music
Games & Puzzles
National
Arts & Entertainment
Kurt Russell: Goldie Hawn's happiness is 'irresistible'
By CelebretainmentUpdated
2 hrs ago
Kurt Russell says Goldie Hawn’s “happiness is irresistible”, as the happy couple gush over one another after 38 years together.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Megan Thee Stallion: Beyonce and Jay-Z give totally different types of advice
Gavin Rossdale: I'm inspired by my kids
Dame Barbara Windsor has died aged 83
Movie review: 'I'm Your Woman' is a little slow and too convoluted, but will keep you on edge
Cassie is pregnant!
Harry Styles has a 'go-with-the-flow attitude towards love'
Meghan Trainor feels she's beating gestational diabetes
Jeannie Mai 'was almost dying' before undergoing surgery
Special Sections
Fact Finder 2020
Spring Home Improvement
Tullahoma Church Guide
Medical Update
Online Features
How Hackers Could Use the Pandemic and Technology Against Us in 2021 [Video]
Brandpoint (BPT)
Dec 9, 2020
Sorry, but your browser does not support the video tag.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
5 ways to experience wine country from home
Sculpt Your Best Body Now: Get Trim and Toned with This Advanced Duo Treatment
Need more functionality? 4 simple ways to upgrade your laundry room
Experiencing Constipation? Make a New Year’s Resolution to Get the Help You Need
Sleep-trainer approved tips for new parents
Fall prevention: Tips to enjoy favorite winter activities safely
BookBites: Four Diverse Stories To Intrigue Readers
Create a plan: Working with a doctor to help manage a chronic inflammatory condition
Classifieds
Place An Ad
Real Estate
Property For Rent
Cars & Vehicles
Jobs
Items For Sale
Pets
The Job Network
Tullahoma News, (Tullahoma News), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Tullahoma News of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.THEREFOREThis Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Tullahoma News, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.tullahomanews.com you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.Collection of InformationThis website collects various types of information, such as:Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.In addition to our own cookies, we may also allow various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the service and deliver targeted advertisements and content on and through the service.Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.Tullahoma News may have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion at a later time. We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.Use of Information CollectedTullahoma News may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.tullahomanews.com . Tullahoma News may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.Tullahoma News does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.Tullahoma News may feel it necessary, from time to time, to make contact with you on behalf of other external business partners with regards to a potential new offer which may be of interest to you. If you consent or show interest in presented offers, then, at that time, specific identifiable information, such as name, email address and/or telephone number, may be shared with the third party.Tullahoma News may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.Tullahoma News may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Tullahoma News and/or our website;Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Tullahoma News; andPerform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.citizentribune.com and/or the general public.Children Under Age of 13Tullahoma News does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.Unsubscribe or Opt-OutAll users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to [Need Email]. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.Links to Other Web SitesOur website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Tullahoma News does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.SecurityTullahoma News shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.Third Party AdvertisersWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please complete the following links:   http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp,   http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.Changes to Privacy Policy AgreementTullahoma News reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at www.tullahomanews.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Tullahoma News decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.Acceptance of TermsThrough the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.Email: info@tullahomanews.comTelephone Number: 931-455-4545Mailing Address:Tullahoma News505 Lakeway Pl.Tullahoma, TN 3738804/10/2018
Latest News
Wildcats notch third-straight win
Dec. 10 COVID-19 Update
Dec. 9 COVID-19 Update
Arrowheads Museum refuses to revert the land back to Coffee County
Man opens fire while high on cocaine
Fans meet ‘Bo Duke’ at movie premiere
Committee nixes bonuses for county employees
Governor authorizes National Guard to help at hospitals
Online Poll
Will you spend $100 or more on any single gift this Christmas season?
You voted:
YES
NO
I won't spend $100 combined
Vote
View Results
Back
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
ArticlesTullahoma teen killed in Decherd crashPolice say no foul play in downtown deathMan opens fire while high on cocaineSlumbering driver caught with drugs and gunsAssimilation - I just want some Doritos!Mall shooting suspect bound on attempted murder chargeMotorcycle club braves cold to help ‘Fill the Semi’Tour of Homes goes virtual with help from Dustin LynchCity hires Samaniego as Senior Planner of community developmentTUA banks on easing traffic with new location
Images
Videos
Featured Businesses
Bethel Baptist Church
408 Westside Dr, Tullahoma, TN 37388
931-454-0837
Website
Center Grove Baptist Church
Market Data by TradingView
Thank you!
As our thanks for being a loyal subscriber, you have been upgraded to our premium service AT NO ADDITIONAL CHARGE! You'll enjoy AD-FREE access to our site as long as you are a paid subscriber. ENJOY!
Upgrade to Premium Service for AD-FREE browsing. Only $2.00 additional per month!
Upgrade Here
or call 931-455-4657 or email kboswell@tullahomanews.com.
Get FULL access to tullahomanews.com with packages starting as low as $3.99 per month!
Get Started!
© Copyright 2020 Tullahoma News, 505 Lakeway Place Tullahoma, TN | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
Notifications
Settings
You don't have any notifications.
Get up-to-the-minute news sent straight to your device.
